Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Radio TV Services records
circa 1937 - 2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Radio TV Services
UA.27.02.0001
36.5 Linear Feet
372 Gigabytes
Established in 1954 as part of the Office of Information Services (now the Office of News and Communications,) Radio TV Services supervises the production of materials for radio and television, assists in the preparation of audio-visual materials needed by the university, and promotes the University's exposure to local, state, and national audiences. It makes documentary films, covers events and functions on campus, sets up news conferences in cooperation with local and national media, interviews university personnel, and provides features on students for their home-town media. Collection includes correspondence, subject files, sound recordings (audiocassettes and reel-to-reel tapes), film (16mm), and video tape (U-Matic and 2-inch quadruplex). Notable people documented on film and tape include Keith Brodie, Terry Sanford, Douglas M. Knight, Orin Pilkey, Robert Menzies, Jerry Falwell, Billy Graham, Queen Noor al Hussein, Jesse Jackson, Waylon Jennings, Juanita Kreps, Robert McNamara, Ronald Reagan, William Westmoreland, Desmond Tutu, Elie Wiesel, Reynolds Price, Martin Luther King, Jr., Hubert Humphrey, Richard Nixon, Stokely Carmichael, Kenneth Clark, Sidney Cohen, Adam Clayton Powell, Betty Friedan, B. F. Skinner, Sam Ervin, Alex Haley, Tom Wolfe, Buckminster Fuller, and Cesar Chavez. Subjects include Duke University basketball, football, commencement, convocation, homecoming, the Epoch Campaign announcement, student unrest in the 60s, the Silent Vigil held after the death of Dr. King, the Duke Marine Laboratory, the discovery of the U.S.S. Monitor, oceanographic research, the 1954 Orange Bowl, Joe College Weekend, various campus scenes, Duke Gardens, and the Richard Nixon Library controversy. Completed films include Response to Our Challenge and This is Duke. English.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Use of audiotapes, films, and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for a few of the films have been made on VHS and DVD, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings and films are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Provenance
The Radio TV Services Records was received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1988; 2008, accession numbers UA88-57, UA2008-0048, UA2008-0065; 2012, accession UA2012-0041.
Historical Note
Established in 1954 as part of the Office of Information Services (now the Office of News and Communications,) Radio TV Services supervises the production of materials for radio and television, assists in the preparation of audio-visual materials needed by the university, and promotes the University's exposure to local, state, and national audiences. Harry Durham was the director from 1964-1966, followed by Charlie Braswell, who held the position until 1988.
The office produced a daily news program, The News of Duke, and a weekly radio program, Challenges in Education (which eventually aired on more than 100 stations, including Voice of America and the Armed Forces Network). It also made documentary films, such as Medicine at the Crossroads (1966). It covers events and functions on campus, including trustee meetings, convocations, and protests. It sets up news conferences in cooperation with local and national media, interviews university personnel, and provides features on students for their home-town media.
Collection Overview
Collection includes correspondence, subject files, images, sound recordings (audiocassettes, reel-to-reel tapes, and digital audio), film (16mm), video tape (U-Matic, 2-inch quadruplex, and digital video), and multimedia of events related to Duke occurring both on and off campus. There is a detailed subject file on index cards for most of the film and some of the sound recordings, as well as other indexes and notes.
Notable people documented on film and tape include Keith Brodie, Terry Sanford, Douglas M. Knight, Orin Pilkey, Robert Menzies, Jerry Falwell, Billy Graham, Queen Noor al Hussein, Jesse Jackson, Waylon Jennings, Juanita Kreps, Robert McNamara, Ronald Reagan, William Westmoreland, Desmond Tutu, Elie Wiesel, Reynolds Price, Martin Luther King, Jr., Hubert Humphrey, Richard Nixon, Stokely Carmichael, Kenneth Clark, Sidney Cohen, Adam Clayton Powell, Betty Friedan, B. F. Skinner, Sam Ervin, Alex Haley, Tom Wolfe, Buckminster Fuller, and Cesar Chavez. There are also film and recordings documenting Duke University basketball, football, commencement, convocation, homecoming, the Epoch Campaign announcement, student unrest in the 60s, the Silent Vigil held after the death of Dr. King, the Duke Marine Laboratory, the discovery of the U.S.S. Monitor, oceanographic research, the 1954 Orange Bowl, Joe College Weekend, various campus scenes, Duke Gardens, and the Richard Nixon Library controversy. Completed films include Response to Our Challenge and This is Duke.
Motion pictures (visual works); Sound recordings; Duke University -- Basketball -- History; Brodie, H. Keith H. (Harlow Keith Hammond), 1939-; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Joe College Weekend; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University -- Football -- History; Duke University. Radio TV Services; King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1929-1968; Duke University. Marine Laboratory -- History; Monitor (Ironclad); Knight, Douglas M., 1921-2005; Menzies, Robert J. (Robert James), 1923-1976; Price, Reynolds, 1933-2011; Sanford, Terry; Pilkey, Orrin H., 1934-
- General Correspondence C-Z, 1964-1973
  Scope and Contents note
  Correspondence files of Harry Durham and Charlie Braswell, directors of Radio TV Services. The A and B folders are missing.
  - Correspondence C-Z (Box 1)
- Subject folders, 1954-1986
  Correspondence, reports, minutes, memoranda, and other materials concerning the campus radio and TV stations, the introduction of FM broadcasting, public relations, film projects, and other activities.
  - Subject Folders A-M (Box 1)
  - Subject Folders N-Z (Box 2)
- Indexes and Notes, 1956-1974 and undated
  - Card File Index (Box 3)
    Extensive subject, and numerical index created by the department. Materials indexed are reel to reel audiotapes (numbered B-1 through B-773), 16mm films (numbered C-1 through C-164 and D-1 through D-8), and scripts (which are not part of the existing collection.) Audio cassettes, some of the 16mm films, and videotapes are not included in the index.
  - C-Series Films: Notes for Subject Index, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - C-Series Films: Title Index, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Continuity: Duke Founder's Day Film (Duke 140), Dec. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Original elements for Duke 140 are in Box 17 and Box 20. Audiotape is in Box 12.
  - D2 and D3: List of Shots, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Typed list of shots for Film D-2 and a handwritten list of shots for Films D-2 and D-3 of Terry Sanford's inauguration. Film D-2 is in Box 15. Film D-3 is missing from the collection.
  - Epoch Campaign Script, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Full title of the script is For Humankind and History: A Time for Greatness at Duke. Film related to the Epoch Campaign is in Box 15 and Box 20. Audiotape of the Epoch Campaign Announcement is in Box 11.
  - Description of Film from the Music Building Dedication, Nov. 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Two-page typewritten list of shots. This film does not exist in the collection.
  - Description of Films (Numbered Series), Nov. 2, 1971, and undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Handwritten and typed list of shots for some of the films in the Numbered Series in Box 15.
  - Letter Re: Quest Without End, Mar. 1, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Quest Without End was a color sound film about Duke University. A copy of the film and its original elements are in Box 18.
  - Mimeographs: Football Games, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Mimeographed shot lists for two of the films in Box 18: Duke vs. N.C. State and Duke vs. South Carolina.
  - News Conference: U.S.S. Monitor, Mar. 7, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Folder containing press releases, correspondence, black and white photographs, and other printed materials.
  - This is Duke, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    A typed description of the film This is Duke plus a xerox copy of an article about the film from the Alumni Register, Sept. 1954.
  - C-160 Shot List, Apr. 28, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    A handwritten list of shots from film #C-160, Presentation Ceremony of some type at Duke Homestead.
  - Cenntennial Year, 1938-1939, Initial Appraisal, Apr. 17, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Sound Recordings, 1960-1988 and undated
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original recordings are closed to use. Digitized access copies are available for some recordings. Please contact University Archives staff for more information.
  In addition to individuals related to Duke such as Keith Brodie, Terry Sanford, and Douglas M. Knight, a number of other notable people are represented in the sound recordings: Jerry Falwell, Billy Graham, Queen Noor al Hussein, Jesse Jackson, Waylon Jennings, Juanita Kreps, Robert McNamara, Ronald Reagan, William Westmoreland, Desmond Tutu, Elie Wiesel, Reynolds Price, Martin Luther King, Jr., Hubert Humphrey, Richard Nixon, Stokely Carmichael, Kenneth Clark, Sidney Cohen, Adam Clayton Powell, Betty Friedan, B. F. Skinner, Sam Ervin, Alex Haley, Tom Wolfe, Buckminster Fuller, and Cesar Chavez. There are also tapes pertinent to Duke University basketball, commencement, student unrest in the 60s, the Silent Vigil held after the death of Dr. King, the discovery of the U.S.S. Monitor, and oceanographic research.
  - Cassettes, 1970-1988, undated; 4.1
    Arrangement
    Arranged in the original alphabetical order in which they were received.
    - AT, Oct. 14, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0020)
    - American Dance Festival. News Conference, circa 1978 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0021)
    - American Musical Theatre. News Conference, Sept. 23, 1977 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0022)
    - Manny Azenberg meets press, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0023)
    - Basketball Team returns from Final Four. Event, Apr. 2, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0024)
    - Basketball Team returns from Final Four in Kansas City. Event, Apr. 15, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0025)
    - Dr. Brodie. First talk to Academic Council. Address, Sept. 26, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0026)
    - Brodie. Inauguration, Sept. 28, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0027)
    - Brodie, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0028)
    - Dr. Keith Brodie named President of Duke. News Conference, Dec. 4, 1984 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0029)
    - Dr. Brodie's first public talk. Welcome Freshmen. Address, Aug. 21, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0030)
    - Bryan Center. Dedication, Feb. 26, 1982 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0031)
    - Bryan Research Building Groundbreaking, Feb. 12, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0032)
    - Dr. Z. Brzezinski, Former National Security Advisor to President Carter. News Conference, Dec. 9, 1987 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0033)
    - Carol Burnett. News Conference, Apr. 10, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0034)
    - Campaign for Arts Sciences, $200 million. News Conference, Dec. 4, 1984 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0035)
    - CAMA. Tape 1, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0036)
    - CAMA. Tape 2, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0037)
    - CAMA. Tape 3, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0038)
    - CAMA. Tape 4, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0039)
    - CAMA. Tape 5, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0040)
    - A.Calero. Contra. News Conference, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0041)
    - A.Calero (Contra) to students. Page Auditorium, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0042)
    - Chronicle. 75th Anniversary. Tape 1, Nov. 14, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0043)
    - Chronicle. 75th Anniversary. Tape 2, Nov. 14, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0044)
    - 5 Years of Coastal Zone Management. Media Briefing. Tape 6 of 7, Mar. 29, 1980-Mar. 30, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0045)
    - 5 Years of Coastal Zone Management. Media Briefing. Tape 7 of 7, Mar. 29, 1980-Mar. 30, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0046)
    - Commencement: Heard, 1975 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0047)
    - Commencement: Sanford, 1976 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0048)
    - Commencement: Kreps, 1977 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0049)
    - Commencement. Tape 2 only, 1978 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0050)
    - Commencement. Tape 1, 1979 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0051)
    - Commencement. Tape 2, 1979 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0052)
    - Commencement. Tape 1 only, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0053)
    - Commencement. Tape 1, 1981 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0054)
    - Commencement. Tape 2, 1981 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0055)
    - Commencement. Tape 1, 1982 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0056)
    - Commencement. Tape 2, 1982 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0057)
    - Commencement. Tape 1, 1983; 1:32:53 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0058, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0002, Audio-file ua27020001_cs_0058_001.wav, Audio-file ua27020001_cs_0058_002.wav)
    - Commencement. Tape 2, 1983; 0:33:33 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0059, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0003, Audio-file ua27020001_cs_0059_001.wav)
    - Commencement. Tape 1 only (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0060)
    - Commencement. Tape 1, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0061)
    - Commencement. Tape 2, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0062)
    - Commencement, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0063)
    - Commencement: Ted Koppel, 1987 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0064)
    - Commencement: Garry Trudeau, 1988 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0065)
    - Duke North (Hospital): plans to open. News Conference, Jan. 14, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0066)
    - 50th Anniversary of Duke. Symposium. Tape 1, Apr. 11, 1980-Apr. 12, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0067)
    - 50th Anniversary of Duke. Symposium. Tape 2, Apr. 11, 1980-Apr. 12, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0068)
    - 50th Anniversary of Duke. Symposium. Tape 3, Apr. 11, 1980-Apr. 12, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0069)
    - 50th Anniversary of Duke. Symposium. Tape 4, Apr. 11, 1980-Apr. 12, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0070)
    - 50th Anniversary of Duke. Symposium. Tape 5, Apr. 11, 1980-Apr. 12, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0071)
    - C. A. Dukes. Talks regarding 1938 film on Duke University, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0072)
    - Dr. R. Eisenson, DUMC. News Conference, Mar. 5, 1987 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0073)
    - Reverend Jerry Falwell. News Conference, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0074)
    - For Humankind and History, Sept. 1975 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0075)
    - For Humankind and History. Tape 1, Sept. 1976 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0076)
    - For Humankind and History. Tape 2, Sept. 1976 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0077)
    - Founder's Days Convocation, Dec. 11, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0078)
    - Founder's Days Convocation, Dec. 10, 1987 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0079)
    - Fuqua, $4 million gift from R. David Thomas (Wendy's). News Conference, June 13, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0080)
    - Fuqua Business School. Dedication, Apr. 1983 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0081)
    - J. B. Fuqua. News Conference, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0082)
    - Fuqua School of Business. Groundbreaking, Feb. 18, 1981 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0083)
    - Pamela Gann, New Law Dean Introduced, May 9, 1988 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0084)
    - Dr. Billy Graham. News Conference, Nov. 19, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0085)
    - Former Senator Gary Hart. Major Speaker Series, Jan. 27, 1987 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0086)
    - Hemo Sponge, Dr. Bonaventura, Marine Lab. News Conference, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0087)
    - Queen Noor Al Hussein. Address, Apr. 16, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0088)
    - Hyperbonic Chamber, 1981 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0089)
    - Jesse Jackson. Tape 1, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0090)
    - Jesse Jackson. Tape 2, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0091)
    - Waylon Jennings. News Conference, Sept. 9, 1987 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0092)
    - Surgeon General Koop. News Conference, Feb. 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0093)
    - J. Kreps, Secretary of Commerce. Address, May 8, 1977 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0094)
    - J. Kreps, Secretary of Commerce. Address, Oct. 19, 1977 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0095)
    - Ann Landers. News Conference, Feb. 12, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0096)
    - Arthur Larson. International Law, Sept. 1970 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0097)
    - Jack Lemmon, Jonathan Miller. Play. News Conference, Mar. 10, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0098)
    - Robert McNamara. News Conference, Oct. 15, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0099)
    - Moroccan Ambassador. News Conference, Sept. 13, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0100)
    - Nixon Library. Alex McMahon, Chairman of the Board. News Conference, Sept. 4, 1981 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0101)
    - Nixon Library. Alex McMahon, Chairman of the Board. News Conference, Sept. 14, 1981 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0102)
    - Nixon Library. Alex McMahon, Chairman of the Board. News Conference, Oct. 6, 1981 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0103)
    - Dr. William O'Barr. ABC Radio, Feb. 6, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0104)
    - Earl Owensby, movies. News Conference, Jan. 30, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0105)
    - Dr. Chris Quigg, Dr. Goshaw: Super Conducting Super Collider. News Conference, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0106)
    - President Ronald Reagan at Duke. Substance Abuse. Copy 1, Feb. 8, 1988 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0107)
    - President Ronald Reagan at Duke. Substance Abuse. Copy 2, Feb. 8, 1988 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0108)
    - Regional sports arena. Discussion, Apr. 2, 1979 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0109)
    - Terry Sanford. News Conference, Jan. 13, 1976 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0110)
    - Terry Sanford to Duke Faculty. Address, Sept. 25, 1975 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0111)
    - Terry Sanford to 1976 CASE. Address (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0112)
    - Sanford Returns to Duke, Jan. 26, 1976 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0113)
    - President Sanford to Faculty Meeting, Oct. 30, 1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0114)
    - President Sanford to Alumni. Final Talk, June 8, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0115)
    - D. Seaver and T. Sanford, Dec. 1974 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0116)
    - Shevchensko, Former Soviet Ambassador to U.N. News Conference, Apr. 1987 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0117)
    - Neil Simon and Gene Saks. Broadway Bound. News Conference, Oct. 3, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0118)
    - Eleanor Smeal, President of NOW. News Conference, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0119)
    - Soccer Team Reception, NCAA Champs, 1st Duke team to win, 1986 December 15 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0120)
    - John Spencer: Last Leonardo da Vinci Found. News Conference, circa 1979-1980 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0121)
    - Dr. Stern of Burroughs Corporation. News Conference, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0122)
    - Teer Engineering Library. Dedication, Sept. 7, 1984 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0123)
    - Thelonius Monk Institute of Jazz. News Conference, June 20, 1988 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0124)
    - Bishop Tutu in Duke Chapel. Address, Jan. 19, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0125)
    - Bill van Alstya to VOA, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0126)
    - Video History Archive. Dedication, Nov. 21, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0127)
    - Alvin Weingerg, Nuclear Energy. News Conference, Mar. 14, 1986 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0128)
    - General William Westmoreland. Address, Sept. 19, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0129)
    - Elie Wiesel. Major Speakers, Sept. 15, 1987; 1:12:11 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0130, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0004, Audio-file UA27020001-CS-0130_001.wav, Audio-file UA27020001-CS-0130_002.wav)
    - Mr. Wyman, CBS Board Chairman. Address, Feb. 5, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0131)
    - Mr. Wyman, CBS Board Chairman. News Conference, Feb. 5, 1985 (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0132)
    - Unknown, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0133)
    - Unknown, undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette UA27020001-CS-0134)
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes, 1960-1975; undated; 4.2
    Scope and Contents
    All audiotapes in this series are 1/4 inch tape on open reels. Reels are 7 inch except where noted. This series is indexed by title and by subject in the card file index in Box 3.
    Reel-to-reel audiotapes were originally numbered B-1 through B-773. That arrangement has been retained here. Approximately twenty un-numbered tapes are listed at the end of the series in the same order in which they were received.
    - Submillimeter Waves, Dr. Walter Gordy, April 14, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0001)
      Original identification number: B-3
    - Interview with Dr. Knight and Charlie Harville, ACC Sportscaster, undated (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0002)
      Original identification number: B-5
    - Dr. Knight. Interview by Mr. Clarence Whitfield, March; 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0003)
      Original identification number: B-10
    - Oceanography: Eastward Launching, Sturgeon Bay, Wisconsin, May 9, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0004)
      Original identification number: B-16
    - Duke Ambassadors, Jan. 10, 1960 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0005)
      Original identification number: B-19
    - Day: Mr. George V. Allen - main address, WDBS radio recording, 1961 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0006)
      Original identification number: B-20
    - Dr. Knight's 1st Press Conference as President, Sept. 3, 1963 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0007)
      Original identification number: B-21
    - Knight's Inauguration Dinner, Dec. 10, 1963 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0008)
      Original identification number: B-22